After Everything is a romance, drama film directed by Castille Landon.
Besieged by writer’s block and the crushing breakup with Tessa, Hardin travels to
Portugal in search of a woman he wronged in the past – and to find himself.
Hoping to win back Tessa, he realizes he needs to change his
ways before he can make the ultimate commitment.
Hardin Scott, played by Hero Fiennes Tiffin.
Tessa Young, played by Josephine Langford.
Nathalie, played by Mimi Keene.
Christian Vance, played by Stephen Moyer.
Trish Daniels, played by Louise Lombard.
Kimberly Vance, played by Arielle Kebbel.
After Everything is a 2023 American romantic drama film written and directed by Castille
Landon, based on the characters from the After series of novels by Anna Todd.
The direct sequel to After Ever Happy (2022) and the fifth installment the After film series, it stars Josephine
Langford and Hero Fiennes Tiffin reprising their roles as Tessa Young and Hardin Scott, respectively.
The film was released in select theaters in the United States
on September 13, 2023, by Voltage Pictures.
The film explores themes of alcohol, forgiveness,
lisbon, portugal, trauma, writer's block.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.